24小时
第三季  第10集
前情提要
-朱莉娅  -总统先生
-Julia.  -Mr President.
大卫想知道为什么我要他解雇韦恩
David is wondering why I want him to fire Wayne.
韦恩和我坠入爱河
Wayne and I became involved.
他们发生了关系!
They had an affair!
我以为你会赞同我 大卫 没有我的支持
I think you'll agree, David. You wouldn't be where you are
这些年你走不到这一步
without my support over the years.
我从来不求回报
I've never asked you for anything in return.
除了现在 我要求解雇韦恩!
But I'm asking you now. Fire Wayne!
我很抱歉 艾伦 我做不到
Sorry Allan, I can't do that.
你也了解我 知道这样做会有什么结果
Then you know me well enough not to be surprised if there are repercussions.
鲍尔和萨拉扎兄弟一起在墨西哥
Bauer was with the Salazar brothers in Mexico.
他的跟踪器失灵了
His transponder signal stopped working.
我们尽一切可能和他联系
We're doing everything we can to re-establish contact.
让特种部队在收到我消息前 原地待命
Tell the delta units to hold their position till I get back to you.
金 你知道怎么进行频带扫描么?
Kim. Do you know how to do a frequency scan?
知道
Yeah.
好吧 我们在找你父亲的信号 米歇尔 已经在做了
We're trying to pick up your father's transponder signal. Michelle's already begun the scan.
配合她
Coordinate with her.
我有杰克的消息 杰克想要拿到
I have a message from Jack. The virus that they're going to buy
他们交易的病毒
Jack is going to take it from them.
杰克保证如果我帮你 就带着我全家离开
Jack promised to get me and my family out of here if I help you.
那就帮我!
Then help me!
情况变复杂了 另一个买家也想要病毒
There's been a complication. Another buyer's interested in the virus.
我们决定进行拍卖 病毒会给出价最高的一方
We'll hold an auction and the virus will go to the highest bidder.
你们开价2亿2千5百万 她的是2亿4千万
Your bid is 225 million dollars. And hers is 240.
尼娜 你赢了
Nina, you win.
你对我们已经没有利用价值了 你失败了!
You are no use to us anymore. You failed!
拉姆 别这么做
Ramon, don't do this!
5小时前 你还被关在美国监狱 你之所以能自由是因为我救你出来!
Five hours ago you were in an American prison. And now you're free because I broke you out!
我们还能弄到病毒
We can get the virus.
怎么弄?
How do you get the virus?
那个女的 尼娜 如果我失败了 要杀要剐随你
The woman, Nina. If I fail you get to kill me, fine.
但是如果我成功了 那么这宗生意就能继续 一切会步入正轨
But if I succeed the deal will go forward and we'll be back on track.
我们都能分到钱!
We'll all get paid!
以下事件发生于晚上10点至11点之间
The following takes place between 10:00 pm and 11:00 pm.
还有多少人来?
How many more coming, huh?
是美国人还是联邦特工 或者都有?
Are they Americanos or federales or both?
我们进行得怎么样了?
Where are we on this?
已知杰克的最后地点是这儿
Jack's last known position is here.
国安局宣称他们可以重新定位卫星
NSA says they might be able to re-position the satellite
但是在卫星要绕地两周才能到位
but it's going to take at least two orbits to get it over the area.
不行 这样来不及
No, it'll be too late.
估计病毒交易者看准卫星的监视空档才选在这里
Sporadic satellite cover's just probably why the sellers of the virus chose it as a place to meet.
是赫克托打来的
It's Hector.
先把电话接进跟踪系统再接
Throw the call through our system before you answer it.
要尽全力跟踪到这个电话
I want to trace this on the whole networks.
记住 你得想好怎么解释这两小时你渺无音讯
Remember, you're gonna need an explanation he ain't heard from you in over two hours.
搞定了
All set.
-奥尔特加  -盖尔? 到底怎么回事? 我们一直在找你
-Ortega.  -Gael? What's going on? We're trying to reach you.
我之前在分局 不能联系
I was at Division of the Bureau, chief. I couldn't talk.
出事了么?
Is there a problem?
没有 我现在已经回到反恐局了
No, I'm back at CTU, now.
-没人怀疑你为我们工作吧?  -如果有 我们就没机会这样谈了
-Nobody suspects you of working with us?  -If they did, we wouldn't be having this conversation.
听着 我们这儿出问题了
All right, listen. We have a problem.
卖家把我们耍了 另一个买家介入了
The seller double-crossed us. Brought in a second bidder.
另一个买家?
A second bidder?
是的 某个叫尼娜·迈尔斯的女人
Yeah, some woman named Nina Myers.
阿马多尔举行了拍卖 结果我们输了
Amador held an auction. We lost.
-你们没拿到病毒?  -没有
-So you don't have the virus?  -No.
你要我做什么?
What do you want me to do?
鲍尔说他认识这个女人 尼娜
Bauer says he knows this woman, Nina.
我们试图跟踪她 别挂
We're going to try to get into her. Hold on.
-盖尔 我是杰克  -杰克?
-Gael, it's Jack.  -Jack?
听着 我现在给你几分钟前迈克尔 阿马多尔用过的手机号码
Look, I'm gonna give you a number to a cell phone that Michael Amador's been using for the last few hours.
查出他的位置
I want you to ping it until you can get his location.
-号码是011525532240135  -明白
-Number's 011525532240135.  -Got it.
喂? 你还好么?
Hey? Are you all right?
还好 等你找到位置后 和我联系
Yeah. Get back to me on this number as soon as you've got his location.
还有一件事 鲍尔的搭档来过了
One more thing. Bauer's partner showed up.
-你抓住他了?  -是的
-You have him?  -Yes, we have him.
-还活着?  -暂时是
-Alive?  -Yes, for now.
他是独自行动还是会有增援部队?
Is he working alone or does he have back up?
蔡斯·埃德蒙兹隶属外勤部 我无权过问
Chase Edmunds is in Field Ops. I don't have access to the mandate.
你给我查出来 明白么? 我付钱给你干吗的?
You get access, ok? What am I paying you for?
如果我这么做 会暴露身份的
If I try it might blow my cover.
最好是留他一命 直到我们查出来
Best bet is to keep Edmunds alive until we find out.
好吧
All right.
-你找到杰克的位置了么?  -这儿
-Do you have a location on Jack?  -Here.
距我们最后的联系位置 4英里处
About 4 miles from our last contact link.
好! 让特种部队调整位置待命
All right! Tell the delta units to adjust their position and wait for federal orders.
-用三角定位测量法找阿马多尔的电话  -明白
-Run a pass of triangulation on Amador's phone.  -Got it.
金.
Kim
我们找到你父亲了
We found your father.
他正潜伏在萨拉扎身边 他还好
He's undercover with the Salazars. He's fine.
感谢上帝! 蔡斯呢?
Ah, thank God! What about Chase?
他被抓住了
He's been captured.
抓住了? 他还好么?
Captured? Is he ok?
还活着 他们正看着他
He's alive. They're holding him.
-"看着他"是什么意思?  -我推测他们正在拷问他
-What do you mean by "holding him"?  -My guess is they're interrogating him.
我们一得到病毒 就去救蔡斯
Unless we get the virus, we're going for Chase.
-谢谢你告诉我这些  -没关系
-Thank you for not keeping this from me.  -Sure.
你还有什么事么?
Do you need anything else?
不 只是看看你是否还好
No. Just making sure you're ok.
我没事 谢谢
I'm fine. Thank you.
你告诉她了?
Did you tell her?
-蔡斯的事  -没提尼娜吧?
-About Chase, yeah.  -But not about Nina?
没有 她现在不知为妙
No. She doesn't need to know about that now.
杰克! 跟踪阿马多尔的电话要多久?
Jack! How long will it take to trace Amador's phone?
如果一切顺利 10分钟
If everything goes right, 10 minutes.
我得给客户打电话 告诉他们要延期了
I'm going to call our clients. Tell them there's been a delay.
我去看看他们从他搭档嘴里掏出什么了
I'll see if they're getting anywhere with his partner.
好 我们走
Good. Let's go.
-赫克托!  -塞尔吉奥? 你在这儿干吗?
-Hector!  -Sergio? What are you doing here?
我姐姐说我们要走 她要带着我和爸爸离开你
My sister says we're going. She's taking me and my father away from you.
-她说什么时候走么?  -很快 但是我不想离开你赫克托
-Did she say when this will happen?  -Soon. But I don't wanna leave you, Hector.
我不会让这发生的
I would never let that happen.
好了 现在你回去睡觉 但是别告诉你姐姐 行么?
Ok, now, you go back to bed. But don't tell your sister anything about this, ok?
-我会解决一切的  -你会和她谈谈?
-And I'll make sure everything works out.  -You'll talk to her?
对 我会说服她的 来吧
Yes, I'll talk to her, ok? Come on.
蔡斯 怎么样?
How is Chase?
他还挺着
Holding on.
我很快就得和拉姆一起去拿病毒 你只要一有机会就离开这里
I'm gonna go with Ramon to pick up the virus soon. The second you've got a chance to get out of here
带着蔡斯 让他通知反恐局 他们会通知他在哪里
you take it. Go down, get Chase, tell him to call CTU. They'll let him know how to get in touch
与救援队碰头
with the rescue units.
我们会带着你和你全家离开这儿
We'll get you and your family out of here.
你计划去哪儿?
You planning on going somewhere?
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
别装糊涂 娘们
Don't play games with me, woman.
装糊涂? 你到底在说什么?
Play games with me? What are you talking about?
塞尔吉奥告诉我 他正打包去洛杉矶
Sergio tells me he was packing a bag to LA.
有什么好笑的?
What's so funny?
他最近很淘气 你把他教坏的
He was being bad. Something he picked up from you, I think.
我告诉他 我要把你们两个分开 让他别学坏
I told him I was taking him away from you. I was trying to keep him in line.
是吗? 你只是想让他学乖?
That's all? You were trying to keep him in line?
他说想要把枪 我不同意 他就无理取闹
He said he wanted a gun like yours. I said no, he got nasty.
所以 我就吓唬了他一下
So, I scared some sense into him.
他是个好孩子 别这样吓他
He's a good boy. Don't scare him like that.
别怂恿他玩枪
Don't encourage him to play with guns.
杰克!
Jack!
怎么?
Yeah?
我们走!
Let's go!
-亚当说我们联系上杰克了?  -对 刚收到他的消息
-Adam says we're back in touch with Jack?  -Yeah, we just heard from him.
-跟踪病毒进展如何  -我们有卖家的号码了
-How close are we to the virus?  -We have a phone number of the seller.
他叫迈克尔 阿马多尔 我们正对他进行追踪
A Michael Amador. We're running a pass of triangulation right now.
-然后呢?  -我们会把他的位置告知杰克
-Then what?  -We pass the location of Amador onto Jack.
然后一切由杰克定夺
And let Jack call the shots.
好 我让各部门全力以赴
All right. I'll bring division up to speed.
瑞恩 还有一件事 我们刚发现还有一人参与交易
Ryan, there's one more thing. We just found out that there's another player in the deal.
谁?
Who is it?
尼娜·迈尔斯
Nina Myers.
我以为她得到赦免后 一直被禁足在北非
I thought we had her restricted to North Africa after the president gave her exile and immunity.
没错 可目前看来她已经溜掉了
We did. Apparently she slipped out.
杰克会试图与其合作
Jack's trying to get her to help him.
合作? 她杀了杰克的妻子 说服她可不容易
Help him? She killed his wife, that's a hard sell.
我也不知巨细
I don't know the details.
金知道么?
Does Kim know about it?
不 我现在不想告诉她
No. I'd like to keep it that way for now.
好吧 有情况和我联系
All right. Keep me updated.
-我得向你道歉  -不用
-I owe you an apology.  -You don't.
听着 如果你认为我不胜任这份工作 你自然有权利上报
Look, if you thought I wasn't fit to do my job then you had a duty to report it.
但你应该明白 我绝不会牺牲这单位的效率
But you should know that I would never risk the effectiveness of this unit
仅仅为了证明我很能挺
just to prove how tough I am.
-我明白 我只是想...  -我知道你在想什么!
-I know that. I just felt that...  -I know what you felt!
你已经说得很清楚了
You made that perfectly clear.
-喂?  -对不起 请让米歇尔过来一下
-Yeah?  -Excuse me, sir. We need Michelle downstairs, please.
好吧
Yeah, all right.
什么? 你说什么: 你要走?
What? What do you mean: you have to go?
萨拉 我手头正忙 不能随便抽身走人
Sarah, I'm in a middle of a crisis, here. I can't just get up and leave.
你现在在哪儿?
Where are you now?
天呐! 好吧
For God sake! All right. Ok.
很倔强
Pretty stubborn, jefe.
让开!
Move!
反恐局并没有安排你走这趟
CTU doesn't have your travel plans in your records.
是你自个儿来的?
Did you come down here by yourself?
老实招吧 免得吃苦
Tell me. And this will all be over.
你是自个儿来的?
Did you come down here by yourself?
继续 如果他还挺得住 就用汽油
Keep at it. If he doesn't crack soon, use gasoline.
所有的人员都在忙这件事?
Are all the agencies up to speed on this?
是的 他们和部队合作 包围了病毒
Yes they coordinating with the military to put a net around the virus.
墨西哥政府呢?
What about the Mexican government?
全力合作 他们给了我们自主行动的权利
Full cooperation. They've given us a free hand.
总统先生 我能和你谈谈么?
Mr President. May I please have a word?
-谢谢 格里  -应该的
-Thank you, Gerry.  -Sir.
谢谢 格里
Thanks, Gerry.
我刚和沙利文通话 他撤回他的投票
I just got off the phone with Sullivan. He's pulling his vote.
我们一共失去几位议员支持?
How many senators have we lost?
3位 都是受米利肯操控的人
Three. All proteges of Milliken's.
大卫 我很抱歉 如果米利肯从中作梗 我们的医疗方案无法通过
David, I'm sorry but unless Milliken calls off his dogs, we're not gonna get health care passed.
这是在糟蹋几百万人的福祉!
Sabotaging the bill that can benefit millions of people!
不 他只是在告诉你
No, what he's doing is showing you that
他不仅有能力扶你上台 也能拖你下台
not only did he have the power to help start your political career but he also has the power to put an end to it.
大卫 你不能输了竞选
David, you can't afford to lose this debate
不能毁了你至今坚持的政策宗旨
and fail at getting the most important legislation of your presidency through.
与基勒的竞争 已经稳操胜券
We'd be handing Keeler this election.
我们至今没有输过议员选举
We haven't lost a senate vote yet.
我们会的
We will.
除非你满足他的要求解雇我 否则会输
Unless you give in to his demands and fire me, we will.
大卫 你别无选择
David, you don't have a choice, here.
我告诉过你 我不予考虑
I told you before, that's not an option.
听着 我知道你想为我主持公道
Listen, I... I know you wanna do the right thing by me.
但是我确实犯了错
But I'm the one who made this mistake.
我和米利肯妻子的外遇是愚蠢至极
My affair with Milliken's wife was stupid and wrong.
没错
Yes, it was.
但他的所作所为更加过分
But what he's trying to do is worse.
为了私人报复 他宁可扼杀
For personal revenge he's willing to kill a piece of legislation
造福全国的政策
that's good for this country.
我们不能允许这样的事发生
And we can't let that happen.
肯定有办法对抗他
There has to be a way to get to him.
-怎么  -议员海耶斯找您
-Yes.  -I have senator Hayes for you, sir.
-议员先生  -总统阁下
-Senator.  -Mr President.
把它们堆在那儿 我几分钟内就回来
No, push them all onto stacks, I'll be back in a couple of minutes.
照我说的办 贾斯廷
No, just what I said. Learn to follow instructions, Justin.
我完全有权利向你发火
I have every right to be angry with you.
对不起 但是我和你说了 家里有麻烦了
I'm sorry but I told you, it's a family emergency.
现在你导致我家也有麻烦了 不是么?
Well there are two family emergencies now, aren't there?
嗨 小姑娘!
Hi, baby girl!
而且两者之中 你的并没有那么重要 不是么?
And out of the two, yours is less important, don't you think?
对我来说不是
Not to me, it's not!
你的工作保不住了
Your job is in serious jeopardy.
谁理你!
Whatever!
赫克托! 我们从埃德蒙兹那儿知道什么?
Hector! What did you learn from Edmunds?
他就算手上挨了一枪都不肯吐露消息
He can take a bullet through the hand without saying anything useful.
盖尔?
Gael?
我们正在跟踪阿马多尔
Yeah, we're tracking Amador.
他在帕洛贝尔德北面7英里的郊区高速公路向西移动
He's seven miles North of Palo Verde, moving west on the rural highway.
知道他去哪儿么?
Any idea where he's going?
不知道 等他停下后和我联系
No. Just get back to me as soon as he's stopped.
他们找到了阿马多尔
They've located Amador.
他在帕洛贝尔德北面7英里的高速公路上
He's on a highway, seven miles north of Palo Verde,
向西移动
moving west.
肯定是14号高速公路 我们得出发了 不能让他跑太远
Must be Highway 14. We should get moving. We can't let him get too far ahead.
好 让所有人准备
Ok. Get everyone ready.
不行 在确认他拿到病毒前 不要轻举妄动
No. You can't ambush Amador unless you're absolutely certain that he's got the virus with him.
那你觉得应该怎么做?
What are you saying we should do?
让他带我们去找尼娜
Let him lead us to Nina.
当我们确定他们带着病毒 我们就出击
When we're sure that they've got the virus, then we go in.
不过不能带着一大群人
But not with an army of men.
你得让我单独进去
You have to let me go in alone.
你不许单独行动
You are not going anywhere alone.
我不会让你离开我的视野范围
I'm not letting you out of my sight.
我们一起去
We go together.
赫克托 你最好呆在这儿
Hector, you're better off here.
让所有人做好准备 以防万一
And make sure that everybody is ready just in case.
杰克 把电话给我 你开车
Jack, give me the phone. You're driving.
还睡不着?
Still not asleep?
没事 塞尔吉奥
It's ok, Sergio.
爸爸?
Papa?
他和那人去哪儿?
Where did he go with that man?
我不知道 但是至少他还活着
I don't know. But at least he's still alive.
做好准备 我们要走了
Get everything ready, we're leaving.
拉姆走了 而赫克托正在休息 这是我们最好的机会了
Ramon's got Hector stressing it's our best chance.
不 这不行!
No, we can't!
别争了 我需要你帮助
Please don't argue, I need you to help me.
你要我做什么?
What do you want me to do?
给卡车做手脚 这样他们不能跟着我们
Do something to the truck so they can't follow us.
拔根线什么的 然后让塞尔吉奥安静地做好准备
Pull wires, whatever. Then get Sergio ready and keep him quiet.
带他进卡车里等我
Put him in the truck and wait for me.
你要做什么?
What are you going to do?
我必须做的事 快走
What I have to. Now, go.
小心点
Be careful.
-你有打火机么?  -有
-Do you have a light?  -Sure.
朱莉娅
Julia.
很久不见了
It's been a long time.
你好
Hi.
谢谢你来见我
Thanks for meeting me.
我猜你找我 是因为我丈夫强迫总统解雇你
I guess you're here because my husband's trying to force the president to fire you.
是的 其实除此以外 还有比我的工作更加重要的事
Yeah. Well, there's much more at stake, here, than just my job, you know?
关于我兄弟的问题
It's about my brother.
他坚持自己的信念 运行政权机构
Being able to run his administration however he sees fit.
因此失去一位这样的总统 是美国人民的极大损失
And it's not fair to the people of this country that the president be extorted.
我一直很喜欢你的崇高品质
I do love it when you get all noble.
朱莉娅
Julia.
我应该怎么办?
What am I supposed to do?
-我也无能为力  -不 不是这样
-All this is out of my control.  -No, it's not.
而且我相信你也知道
It's not, and I think you know that.
每个人都认为艾伦支配着你
Everybody thinks Allan dominates you.
实际上 他需要你 你知道这点
The truth is, he needs you, you know that.
告诉他 如果他不收手你就会离开他
Tell him you'll leave him if he doesn't back off.
他不会再相信我了
He'll never believe me.
说服他
Make him believe you.
我想你
I miss you.
你想我么?
Do you miss me?
这又能改变什么?
Oh, what difference would it make?
这能改变很多
It could make a lot of difference.
朱莉娅 停下 我们不能这样
Julia, stop it. We can't.
你想过我么?
Do you think of me?
-别这样  -这只是一个单纯的问题
-Don't do this.  -It's a simple question.
你想过我么?
Do you think about me?
想过
Yes.
是的 我想过你
Yes, I think about you.
但是 这无关紧要
But, it doesn't mean anything.
我一直惦记着你 这是关键
I think about you. And it does mean something.
我不是为此而来
I didn't come here for this.
你来这里有你自己的目的
You came here because you wanted something.
我也是
I want something too.
我喜欢当艾伦·米利肯夫人
I like being Mrs Allan Milliken.
但这并不阻碍我们之间的关系
But that does not have to have anything to do with you and me.
回到我身边
Come back to me.
这是我想要的回报
That's what I want in return.
以前可以 现在也可以
It worked once. It can work again.
这对我永远行不通
It never worked. Not for me.
那我恐怕就无能为力了
Then I'm afraid I can't help you.
告诉我 你个混蛋
Talk to me, you, bastard.
你明不明白
What you don't understand,
您明不明白 如果你不开口 赫克托也会这么对我
what you don't understand, if you don't talk Hector will take it out on me.
-说话啊!  -爱德华多! 退下
-Talk to me!  -Eduardo! Back off.
赫克托 觉得也许他会告诉我
Hector thinks he might talk to me.
他们问什么你就答什么 这样你就不用吃苦头了
Tell these men what they want to know and your suffering will end.
你不会被杀的 我保证
You won't be killed, I swear.
我凭什么相信你?
Why should I believe you?
因为如果你不这么做 他们会活活烧死
Because if you don't, they'll burn you alive.
他很倔强嘛
He's a stubborn one, isn't he?
我们能收拾他
We can handle him.
搜他的口袋 他有手机
Check his pockets. He's got a phone.
桌子上有把枪
There's a gun on the table.
-你在做什么?  -我得止血
-What are you doing?  -I've got to stop the bleeding.
不然我活不了
Or I could die.
快点 我们得走了
Come on. We have to go.
把枪给我
Give me the gun.
躲起来 塞尔吉奥
Stay down, Sergio. Stay down.
-怎么了?  -一切都会好的
-What's going on?  -Everything's gonna be fine.
快点 我们得走了!
Come on! Come on, let's go!
快! 趴下!
Hurry! Get down, get down!
你去哪儿?
Where are you going?
赫克托要我去帮他买点东西.
Hector wants me to pick up something for him.
-什么东西?  -和你没关系
-What?  -It's none of your business.
-爸爸 怎么了?  -没事 塞尔吉奥 趴下
-Papa, what's happening?  -It's ok, Sergio. Stay down.
谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
克萝伊
Chloe.
特种部队到位了么?
Are delta teams in position yet?
是的 他们已经到位了 我们只要一给信号 他们就去接蔡斯
Yes they're in the area. As soon as we give them the ok, they'll go in to pick up Chase.
好吧 通知所有人 要以获取病毒为优先
All right. Make sure everyone knows this is subordonate to obtaining the virus.
是 已经通知了
Yeah, it's in the brief.
一旦我们找到蔡斯 联系总局 地方分部和首席检察院的人
And once we have Chase, link in Division, District and someone from the Attorney General's office.
很多人想听他的解释
A lot of people want answers from him.
-这怎么回事?  -没什么
-What was that?  -Nothing.
这是你孩子么?
Is this your child?
是的 她并没有影响我工作
Yes, and she hasn't been interfering with my work.
理论上 并没有明确规定禁止带着孩子来工作.
Technically there's no specific rule preventing me from bringing her to work...
常识还用规定!
There's no specific rule because it's common sense!
-立刻给我送走!  -如果可以 我早就办了
-Now get rid of it!  -If I could, I would.
不幸的是 因为我保姆的不负责任我才这样
Unfortunately, my babysitter hit me with some very unprofessional behaviour.
我要这个婴儿立刻出去 克萝伊 不然就找人替你
I want the baby out of here, Chloe, now. Or find someone else to do your job.
父母是受法律保护的 夏佩尔先生 你这么做不公平
Parents are a protected group, Mr Shappel. This is not fair.
阿马多尔 从14号公路进入一条小道开了200码后停了
Amador stopped about 200 yards up a dirt road that intersects with highway 14,
在瓜达卢佩牧场西面2英里处
about 2 miles west of Rancho Guadalupe.
干得好 我们会找到他的
Ok, good work. We'll find him.
盖尔说阿马多尔停在前方半英里左右的地方
Gael said Amador stopped about half a mile up the road.
然后我们怎么做?
So, what do we do?
尼娜肯定差不多和他碰面了
Well, Nina's either with him now or she will be any minute.
我们得设法和她单独谈
We've got to find a way to isolate her.
让我用下夜视仪
Let me see the night-scope.
是她 他们两个
It's her. It's her and him.
好了 我该进去了
Ok, I'm ready to go in.
我告诉过你 你不能离开我的视野
I told you. I'm not letting you out of my sight.
拉姆 我是经过特殊训练的
Ramon, I am trained to do this.
如果我一个人进去 也许还有胜算
If I go in myself I might succeed.
如果一起去 我们两个都活不成
If we go in together, both of us will get killed.
要多久?
How long?
视情况而定 听者 你得相信我
As long as it takes. Look, you're gonna have to start trusting me.
我和你一样想要这笔钱
I want this money just as bad as you do.
-拿到病毒我才会相信你  -那就让我去干!
-I'll trust you when we have the virus.  -So let me make that happen!
我保证 我能让她和我们合作
I promise you. I can make her work with us.
可以用夜视仪看着我
You can watch me through the night scope.
只要我一进房子 你就返回大路
As soon as you see that I've entered the building safely, I want you to go back to the main road.
以免阿马多尔把资源都转移 我们得提前准备
Just in case Amador tries to mobilize his resources outside this perimeter, we've got to be ready.
-行么?  -好吧 快去!
-Ok?  -All right, go!
资金随时准备转账 我什么时候能够拿到病毒?
Funds are ready to be transferred. When do I get the virus?
半小时内我会通知你地点
I'll call you with the location in half an hour.
然后你们按约定 先汇一半资金
You'll transfer 50% of the funds then, as agreed.
我不喜欢这样繁琐的手续
I don't like jumping through all these hoops.
这些手续是为了保护我们 尼娜
The hoops are here to protect us, Nina.
只管等我电话
Just wait here for my call.
站住!
Freeze!
别紧张 我没有武器
Just take it easy. Take it easy, I'm unarmed.
萨拉扎 他们让我和你们的雇主安排见面
The Salazars, they just wanted me to set up a meeting with your employer.
尼娜!
Nina!
尼娜 不许动!
Nina, don't move!
放下枪!
Drop the gun!
回教堂
Get back in the church.
坐下
Take a seat.
别担心 如果我想要你命 你已经死了
Don't worry. If I wanted to kill you, you'd be dead by now.
放下箱子
Put the briefcase down.
托尼 是蔡斯的电话 他刚刚打来
Tony, it's Chase. He's just called in.
接过来 蔡斯 你在哪儿?
Throw us the call. Chase, where are you?
我们坐的卡车刚抛锚
The truck we're in broke down.
据我所知 我们在萨拉扎的基地向东面15分钟处
As far as I can tell we're about 15 miles east of Salazar's base camp.
他应该会跟踪电话找来
He should be able to lock on to this cell.
听着 我们那边有特种部队
Now, look, we've got delta teams in the area.
只要一确定位置 我们就派直升机来接你 杰克在哪儿?
We'll send the choppers as soon as we triangulate. What about Jack?
他跟拉姆·萨拉扎去找阿马多尔和病毒了
He went with Ramon Salazar to find Amador and the virus.
-什么时候?  -半小时前
-How long ago?  -About half an hour.
托尼 你能通知直升机 我还有两个人
Tony, can you tell the chopper I'm bringing two people out with me?
和帮我逃脱的女性的遗体
And the body of the woman who helped me escape.
-她是谁?  -克劳迪娅
-Who was she?  -Claudia.
是赫克托 萨拉扎的女朋友 我和她父亲还有弟弟在一起
It's Hector Salazar's girlfriend. I've got her father and her brother.
找到了 有一支部队10分钟内就能赶到
Got him. There's a delta team less than 10 minutes away.
好 你能挺10分钟么?
Right, can you hang tight for ten?
我不知道 让他们尽快过来
I don't know, just get them here.
好好等着 他们已经在路上了
Just sit tight they're on their way.
你能转告金...
Can you tell Kim that...
告诉她等我安全后 我会打给她
Tell her I'll call her when I'm on safe ground.
好的
Yeah, you got it.
克劳迪娅!
Claudia!
杰克 如果你不是来杀我 你来这儿干嘛?
So, Jack, if you didn't come here to kill me, why are you here?
我得和你亲自谈谈
I need to talk to you alone.
这不可能
That's not gonna happen.
你的老板分给你多少?
How much is your buyer paying you?
如果我交出病毒 2百万
2 million. Once I deliver the virus.
萨拉扎肯付更多
The Salazars are willing to pay you a lot more.
多少?
How much more?
-这是算什么?  -闭嘴!
-What is this?  -Shut up!
-根本不该留他一命  -我来处理
-This guy shouldn't be breathing.  -I'm handling it.
多给多少 杰克?
How much more, Jack?
至少比你现在所得的多10倍
At least ten times more than what you're getting paid right now.
真的?
Really?
这笔交易不赖
That's a pretty great deal.
不过 我的老板拿不到病毒怎么办?
Except, what happens when my buyer doesn't get his virus?
你知道他不会放过我的
You know he's just gonna hunt me down and kill me.
你也知道 有了那笔钱你可以消失得无影无踪
You know with that kind of money you could disappear and never be found.
那么你呢?
Yeah, and what about you?
萨拉扎付我的钱 足够我挥霍下半辈子的了
The Salazars are paying me enough money to do whatever I want for the rest of my life.
我不信 杰克 我认为你还是在为反恐局干
I don't believe you, Jack. I think you're still working for CTU.
那你错了!
Well, you're wrong!
得了吧 杰克! 你不是那种会为钱卖命的人!
Come on, Jack! You're not the type of guy to sell out!
你对你祖国忠心耿耿
You'd do anything for your country.
曾经是这样
There was a time when that was true.
但国家怎么回报我的? 我一无所有!
But what did it ever get me? I lost everything!
当我去萨拉扎组织当卧底时 我把灵魂都出卖了!
When I went undercover with the Salazars, I had to give them my soul!
当我把拉姆·萨拉扎抓起来后 等着我的是什么?
When I brought Ramon Salazar in, what was waiting for me?
什么都没有!
No-one! Nothing!
金呢?
What about Kim?
因为她母亲的事 她一生不会原谅我
She never forgave me for what happened to her mother.
我想把大部分的钱给她 作为补偿
I want to give her most of the money, help her try and get through everything that's happened.
就算你现在孤身一个
Ok, so, say you are working alone.
我杀了你妻子
I killed your wife.
我怎么知道你不会一有机会就杀我?
What's gonna keep you from killing me the first chance you get?
我别无选择 我带着拉姆·萨拉扎越狱了
I don't have a choice. I broke Ramon Salazar out of an American prison.
已经回不去了
I can never go back there again.
我是在豪赌!
This is my one shot at a big score!
一切完了后 我保证消失的无影无踪
And after that, I swear to you, I just wanna disappear.
你浪费了很多时间 尼娜
You've wasted enough time, Nina.
你动手 不然我叫人来
You kill him, or I'm calling in.
很好
Fair enough.
你有什么打算 杰克?
What are you up to, Jack?
-我去找朱莉娅了  -什么?
-I went to see Julia.  -What?
只是想看看她是否会帮我们应付艾伦
Just to see if she would help us with Allan.
-然后?  -她不肯
-And?  -She said: no.
听着 我一直在考虑...
Listen, I've been thinking and...
你别无选择 大卫
You don't have an alternative here, David.
这是我桶的乱子 我该付出代价
This is my mess. I'll take the heat.
-让我辞职吧  -也许一切结束后 我会要你辞职
-Let me resign.  -I may ask you to when this is over.
但决不会因为是米利肯逼我这么做
But it won't be because Milliken is forcing my hand.
韦恩! 我也一直在考虑
Wayne! I've been doing some thinking too.
而且确实有出路
And there is an alternative.
如果米利肯想玩阴的
If Milliken wants to play dirty,
那我们就奉陪到底
we have to lower ourselves to his level.
怎么做?
By doing what?
你先离开一下
Give me a moment.
-喂?  -雪莉?
-Hello?  -Sherry?
大卫? 大卫 怎么了?
David? David, what... what's wrong?
我要你帮忙
I need your help.
好吧 我听着
All right, I'm listening.
来市中心 我今晚要和你见面
Come downtown, I need to see you tonight.
说具体点
Tell me more.
我不能在电话上透露更多了
I can't say much over the phone.
不过这和艾伦·米利肯有关
But it's about Allan Milliken.
-好吧  -我会派车接你
-Fine.  -I'll send a car.
-你还真帮萨拉扎越狱了  -我已经和以前不同了
-You really did break Salazar out of prison.  -I'm not the man you knew before.
这我看得出来
Well, I know about that.
为了2千万美金 我会考虑的
For 20 million dollars, I'm gonna keep an open mind.
那么 杰克
So, Jack,
如果要我接受这件事 我得了解一点
if I'm gonna go forward with this, I have to know one thing.
你能不能原谅我杀了特里?
Are you gonna be able to forgive me for killing Terry?
如果我想复仇 尼娜 我早就杀了你了
If I wanted revenge, Nina, I would have killed you already.
你也明白
You know that.
我所想的只是做完这笔生意 然后永远消失
It's like I said. All I wanna do is finish this deal and disappear for good.
证明给我看
Convince me.